Guide to the D'Arcy Masius Benton & Bowles archives, 1929-1995 and undated RL.00314
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Advertisements, 1932-1995
  - Colgate-Palmolive-Peet Company (See also Oversize box OV5)
    - Various shaving products
      - 1935-1940, Consumer and trade newspaper (Box 42)
      - 1935-1940, Trade magazine (Box 42)
      - 1936, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 42)
      - 1937-1939, Consumer magazine (Box 42)
      - 1939-1940, Consumer magazine (Box 42)
    - Other products
      - 1935, Consumer newspaper (Crystal White, Ben Hur soap) (Box 42)
      - 1935, Consumer newspaper (multiple products) (Box 42)
      - 1935-1936, Consumer and trade newspaper (Kirkman's soap), 2 folders (Box 42)
      - 1935-1937, Consumer newspaper (Octagon soap) (Box 42)
      - 1935-1937, Trade magazine (Special Palmolive shampoo) (Box 42)
      - 1935-1938, Trade magazine (multiple products) (Box 42)
      - 1935-1940, Consumer newspaper (multiple products) (Box 42)
      - 1936-1937, Consumer newspaper (Crystal White, Ben Hur soap) (Box 42)
      - 1938-1939, Trade magazine (multiple products) (Box 43)
      - 1938-1940, Consumer newspaper (Halo shampoo) (Box 43)
      - 1938-1940, Consumer newspaper (Octagon soap) (Box 43)
      - 1938-1940, Consumer newspaper (Vel detergent) (Box 43)
      - 1939, Consumer and trade newspaper (Cue dental liquid, Dr. Caldwell's laxative) (Box 43)
      - 1939, Consumer newspaper (Halo shampoo) (Box 43)
      - 1940, Trade magazine (multiple products) (Box 43)
  - Columbia Broadcasting System (See also Oversize box OV5)
    - Corporate advertising
      - 1943, Consumer magazine (Box 43)
      - 1943-1944, Consumer magazine (Box 43)
      - 1944, Consumer newspaper (Box 43)
      - 1945, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 43)
      - 1946, Consumer magazine (Box 43)
    - CBS Records
      - 1940, Consumer magazine (Box 44)
      - 1940, Consumer newspaper (Box 44)
      - 1940-1946, Trade magazine (Box 44)
      - 1940-1946, Trade newspaper (Box 44)
      - 1941, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 44)
      - 1941, Consumer newspaper, 2 folders (Box 44)
      - 1942, Consumer magazine (Box 44)
      - 1943, Consumer magazine (Box 44)
      - 1944-1945, Consumer magazine (Box 44)
      - 1944-1946, Consumer newspaper (Box 44)
      - 1945, Consumer magazine (Box 44)
      - 1946, Consumer magazine (Box 44)
      - 1960, Consumer magazine (Box 44)
  - Continental Baking Company (See also Oversize box OV5)
    - 1932, Consumer newspaper (Wonder Bread), 4 folders (Box 44)
    - 1937, Consumer newspaper (Wonder Bread), 4 folders (Box 45)
    - 1937, Consumer newspaper (Wonder Wheat Bread) (Box 45)
    - 1937, Consumer newspaper (Certified Bread, Holsum Baby Label) (Box 45)
    - 1937, Consumer newspaper (Hostess cakes) (Box 45)
    - 1937, Trade magazine (multiple products) (Box 45)
    - 1937-1940, Trade magazine (multiple products) (Box 45)
    - 1937-1940, Trade newspaper (multiple products) (Box 45)
    - 1938, Consumer magazine (Wonder Bread) (Box 45)
    - 1938, Consumer newspaper (Wonder Bread), 4 folders (Box 45)
    - 1938, Consumer newspaper (multiple products), 4 folders (Box 46)
    - 1938, Consumer newspaper (multiple products) (Box 46)
    - 1939, Consumer newspaper (Wonder Bread) (Box 46)
    - 1939, Consumer newspaper (multiple products) (Box 46)
    - 1940, Consumer newspaper (Wonder Bread) (Box 46)
    - 1940, Consumer newspaper (Wonder Bread, Certified Bread) (Box 46)
  - Continental Oil Company (CONOCO) (See also Oversize boxes OV5-OV6)
    - 1953, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 46)
    - 1953, Consumer and trade newspaper (Box 46)
    - 1953, Trade magazine, 3 folders (Box 46)
    - 1953-1954, Consumer magazine (Box 46)
    - 1954, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 46)
    - 1954, Consumer and trade newspaper (Box 47)
    - 1954, Trade magazine (Box 47)
    - 1955, Consumer magazine, 4 folders (Box 47)
    - 1955-1956, Consumer and trade newspaper (Box 47)
    - 1955-1956, Trade magazine (Box 47)
    - 1956, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 47)
    - 1956, Consumer newspaper, 2 folders (Box 47)
    - 1956, Trade magazine (Box 47)
    - 1957, Consumer magazine, 4 folders (Box 47)
    - 1957-1959, Consumer and trade newspaper (Box 48)
    - 1957, Trade magazine, 2 folders (Box 48)
    - 1958, Consumer magazine (Box 48)
    - 1958, Trade magazine (Box 48)
    - 1959, Consumer magazine (Box 48)
    - 1959, Trade magazine (Box 48)
    - 1960, Consumer magazine (Box 48)
    - 1960, Trade magazine (Box 48)
  - Crowell-Collier Publishing Company (The American Magazine) (See also Oversize box OV7)
    - 1943, Trade magazine (Box 48)
    - 1943-1946, Trade newspaper (Box 48)
    - 1944, Consumer newspaper (Box 48)
    - 1944, Trade magazine, 2 folders (Box 48)
    - 1945, Consumer magazine (Box 48)
    - 1945, Consumer newspaper (Box 48)
    - 1945, Trade magazine, 5 folders (Box 49)
    - 1946-1951, Consumer newspaper (Box 49)
    - 1946, Trade magazine, 5 folders (Box 49)
    - 1947-1948, Consumer magazine (Box 49)
    - 1947, Trade magazine, 3 folders (Box 49)
    - 1948-1949, Trade magazine (Box 49)
    - 1950-1951, Trade magazine (Box 49)
  - Dana Perfumes (See also Oversize box OV7)
    - 1969-1973, Consumer magazine (Ambush) (Box 50)
    - 1969-1973, Consumer magazine (Tabu) (Box 50)
    - 1969, Consumer magazine (Canoe) (Box 50)
    - 1970-1973, Consumer magazine (Canoe) (Box 50)
    - 1970, Consumer magazine (multiple products) (Box 50)
  - Diamond Match Company (See also Oversize box OV7)
    - 1950-1952, Consumer magazine (Box 50)
    - 1950-1951, Consumer newspaper (Box 50)
    - 1950-1951, Trade magazine (Box 50)
    - 1951, Trade newspaper (Box 50)
    - 1952, Consumer newspaper (Box 50)
    - 1952-1953, Consumer newspaper (Box 50)
    - 1952, Trade magazine, 2 folders (Box 50)
    - 1952-1956, Trade newspaper (multiple products) (Box 50)
    - 1953, Consumer magazine (Box 50)
    - 1953-1956, Consumer newspaper (Box 50)
    - 1953, Trade magazine (Box 50)
    - 1954, Consumer newspaper (Box 50)
    - 1954, Trade magazine (Box 50)
    - 1955, Consumer magazine (Box 50)
    - 1955, Trade magazine (Box 50)
    - 1956, Consumer magazine (Box 50)
    - 1956, Trade magazine (Box 50)
  - E.F. Hutton and Company (See also Oversize box OV7)
    - 1969-1970, Consumer magazine (Box 51)
    - 1969-1970, Consumer newspaper (Box 51)
    - 1970, Trade magazine (Box 51)
    - 1971, Consumer magazine (Box 51)
    - 1974, Consumer magazine (Box 51)
    - 1974, Consumer newspaper (Box 51)
    - 1978, Consumer magazine (Box 51)
  - Fiat Motors of North America (See also Oversize box OV7)
    - 1978, Consumer magazine (Brava) (Box 51)
    - 1978, Consumer magazine (Strada) (Box 51)
    - 1978-1979, Consumer magazine (Fiat 128) (Box 51)
    - 1978-1979, Consumer magazine (Fiat X 1/9 (Box 51)
    - 1978, Consumer magazine (multiple products) (Box 51)
    - 1979, Consumer magazine (Fiat 128) (Box 51)
    - 1978-1979, Consumer magazine (Brava) (Box 51)
    - 1978-1979, Consumer magazine (multiple products) (Box 51)
    - 1979, Consumer magazine (Fiat 128) (Box 51)
    - 1979, Consumer magazine (multiple products) (Box 51)
    - 1979, Consumer magazine (Strada) (Box 51)
    - 1979-1980, Consumer magazine (Strada) (Box 51)
    - 1980, Consumer magazine (Spider, X 1/9) (Box 51)
    - 1980, Consumer magazine (multiple products) (Box 51)
  - Florida Citrus Commission (See also Oversize boxes OV7-OV8)
    - 1943-1944, Consumer magazine (Box 52)
    - 1943-1945, Consumer newspaper and magazine (Box 52)
    - 1943, Consumer newspaper (Box 52)
    - 1944, Consumer magazine (Box 52)
    - 1944, Consumer newspaper, 2 folders (Box 52)
    - 1944-1945, Trade magazine (Box 52)
    - 1945, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 52)
    - 1945, Consumer newspaper (Box 52)
    - 1946, Consumer magazine, 1 of 2 folders (Box 52)
    - 1946, Consumer magazine, 2 of 2 folders (Box 53)
    - 1946-1947, Consumer magazine (Box 53)
    - 1946, Consumer newspaper, 4 folders (Box 53)
    - 1946, Trade magazine, 3 folders (Box 53)
    - 1947, Consumer magazine, 3 folders (Box 53)
    - 1947, Consumer newspaper (in Hebrew) (Box 53)
    - 1947, Consumer newspaper, 1 of 3 folders (Box 53)
    - 1947, Consumer newspaper, 2-3 of 3 folders (Box 54)
    - 1947, Trade magazine, 3 folders (Box 54)
    - 1948, Consumer magazine, 3 folders (Box 54)
    - 1948, Consumer newspaper, 3 folders (Box 54)
    - 1948, Trade magazine, 2 folders (Box 54)
    - 1948, Trade newspaper (Box 54)
    - 1949, Consumer magazine, 3 folders (Box 54)
    - 1949, Consumer newspaper, 2 folders (Box 54)
    - 1949, Trade magazine, 2 folders (Box 55)
    - 1949, Trade newspaper (Box 55)
    - 1950, Consumer magazine (Box 55)
    - 1950, Consumer newspaper (Box 55)
    - 1950, Trade magazine, 2 folders (Box 55)
    - 1950, Trade newspaper (Box 55)
    - 1955, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 55)
    - 1955, Consumer newspaper (Box 55)
    - 1955, Trade magazine (Box 55)
    - 1955, Trade newspaper (Box 55)
    - 1956, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 55)
    - 1956, Consumer newspaper (Box 55)
    - 1956, Trade magazine (Box 55)
    - 1956, Trade newspaper (Box 55)
    - 1957, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 55)
    - 1957, Consumer newspaper (Box 55)
    - 1957, Consumer newspaper (in French) (Box 55)
    - 1957, Trade magazine (Box 56)
    - 1957, Trade magazine (in French) (Box 56)
    - 1957, Trade newspaper (Box 56)
    - 1958, Consumer magazine (Box 56)
    - 1958, Consumer newspaper (Box 56)
    - 1958, Trade magazine (Box 56)
    - 1959, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 56)
    - 1959, Consumer newspaper, 2 folders (Box 56)
    - 1959, Trade magazine (Box 56)
    - 1959, Trade newspaper (Box 56)
    - 1960, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 56)
    - 1960, Trade magazine (Box 56)
    - 1960, Trade newspaper (Box 56)
    - 1961, Consumer magazine, 3 folders (Box 56)
    - 1961, Consumer newspaper, 3 folders (Box 57)
    - 1961, Trade magazine (Box 57)
    - 1961, Trade newspaper (Box 57)
    - 1962, Consumer magazine, 3 folders (Box 57)
    - 1962, Consumer magazine (Canadian) (Box 57)
    - 1962, Consumer newspaper (Box 57)
    - 1962, Trade magazine, 2 folders (Box 57)
    - 1963, Consumer magazine (Box 57)
    - 1963, Trade magazine (Box 57)
  - French Government Tourist Office
    - 1952, Consumer magazine (Box 57)
    - 1952, Consumer newspaper (Box 57)
    - 1952-1954, Trade magazine (Box 57)
    - 1953, Consumer magazine (Box 57)
    - 1953, Consumer newspaper (Box 57)
    - 1954, Consumer magazine (Box 57)
    - 1954-1956, Consumer newspaper (Box 57)
    - 1955, Consumer magazine (Box 57)
    - 1955-1957, Trade magazine (Box 57)
    - 1956-1957, Consumer magazine (Box 57)
  - General Aniline and Film Corporation (See also Oversize box OV8)
    - Ansco
      - 1955-1956, Trade magazine (Box 58)
      - 1956, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 58)
      - 1956, Consumer newspaper (Box 58)
      - 1956, Trade magazine, 4 folders (Box 58)
      - 1957, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 58)
      - 1957-1959, Consumer newspaper (Box 58)
      - 1957, Trade magazine, 6 folders (Box 58)
      - 1958-1959, Consumer magazine (Box 59)
      - 1958, Trade magazine, 4 folders (Box 59)
      - 1959, Trade magazine, 4 folders (Box 59)
      - 1959-1960, Trade newspaper (Box 59)
      - 1960, Consumer magazine (Box 59)
      - 1960, Trade magazine, 3 folders (Box 59)
      - 1961, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 59)
      - 1961, Trade magazine (Box 59)
    - Other products
      - 1956, Consumer magazine (Ozalid) (Box 60)
      - 1956, Trade magazine (Ozalid) (Box 60)
      - 1957, Trade magazine (Ozalid) (Box 60)
      - 1957-1959, Consumer magazine (Ozalid, Antara)) (Box 60)
      - 1958, Trade magazine (Ozalid, Antara)) (Box 60)
      - 1959, Trade magazine (Ozalid, Antara)) (Box 60)
      - 1960-1961, Trade magazine (Ozalid) (Box 60)
  - General Electric (See also Oversize box OV8)
    - 1945, Trade magazine, 2 folders (Box 60)
    - 1945-1946, Trade newspaper (Box 60)
    - 1946, Consumer magazine (resin and insulation) (Box 60)
    - 1946, Trade magazine (plastics), 2 folders (Box 60)
    - 1947, Trade magazine (resin and insulation) (Box 60)
    - 1947, Trade magazine (plastics), 2 folders (Box 60)
    - 1948-1952, Consumer magazine (plastics) (Box 60)
    - 1948, Trade magazine (resin and insulation), 2 folders (Box 60)
    - 1948, Trade magazine (plastics) (Box 60)
    - 1949, Trade magazine (resin and insulation) (Box 61)
    - 1949, Trade magazine (plastics) (Box 61)
    - 1950-1957, Consumer newspaper (Box 61)
    - 1950, Trade magazine, 2 folders (Box 61)
    - 1950, Trade magazine (Box 61)
    - 1950-1952, Trade newspaper (plastics) (Box 61)
    - 1951, Trade magazine, 2 folders (Box 61)
    - 1952, Trade magazine (plastics) (Box 61)
    - 1952, Trade magazine, 2 folders (Box 61)
    - 1953-1954, Consumer magazine (Box 61)
    - 1953, Trade magazine (plastics) (Box 61)
    - 1953, Trade magazine (Box 61)
    - 1953-1956, Trade newspaper (Box 61)
    - 1954, Trade magazine, 2 folders (Box 61)
    - 1955-1956, Consumer magazine (Box 62)
    - 1955, Trade magazine, 3 folders (Box 62)
    - 1956, Trade magazine (Box 62)
  - General Foods (See also Oversize boxes OV8-OV11)
    - Corporate and multiple product
      - 1932-1938, Trade magazine (Box 62)
      - 1933-1937, Trade newspaper (Box 62)
      - 1935-1946, Consumer newspaper (Box 62)
      - 1939-1943, Consumer magazine (Box 62)
      - 1941-1947, Trade magazine (Box 62)
      - 1948, Trade magazine (Box 62)
      - 1949, Trade magazine (Box 62)
      - 1950-1953, Trade magazine (Box 62)
      - 1955-1957, Trade magazine (Box 62)
      - 1955-1958, Trade magazine (Box 62)
      - 1956-1960, Consumer magazine (Box 62)
      - 1956-1959, Trade magazine (Box 62)
      - 1960-1961, Trade magazine (Box 63)
      - 1962-1963, Trade magazine (Box 63)
      - 1970-1981, Consumer magazine (Box 63)
      - 1971-1979, Consumer newspaper (Box 63)
    - Birds Eye frozen foods
      - 1945-1972, Consumer newspaper and magazine (seafood, pizza, Stix) (Box 63)
      - 1960-1961, Consumer newspaper and magazine (frozen instant baby food) (Box 63)
      - 1964-1966, Consumer newspaper and magazine (Soda Burst) (Box 63)
      - 1966-1968, Consumer magazine (Cool Whip) (Box 63)
      - 1966-1969, Consumer newspaper (Cool Whip) (Box 63)
      - 1968-1970, Consumer newspaper and magazine (Cool 'n Creamy Pudding) (Box 63)
      - 1968-1979, Consumer magazine (Orange Plus) (Box 63)
      - 1969-1976, Consumer magazine (Orange Plus) (Box 63)
      - 1969, Consumer magazine (Cool Whip) (Box 63)
      - 1970-1972, Consumer magazine (Cool Whip) (Box 63)
      - 1973-1981, Consumer newspaper (Cool Whip) (Box 63)
      - 1976-1980, Consumer magazine (Cool Whip) (Box 63)
      - 1983-1984, 1994-1995, Consumer magazine (Cool Whip) (Box 63)
    - Certo and Sure-Jell
      - 1932, Consumer magazine (Box 64)
      - 1932, Consumer newspaper (Box 64)
      - 1934-1935, Consumer magazine (Box 64)
      - 1934-1935, Consumer newspaper (Box 64)
      - 1935, Consumer magazine (Box 64)
      - 1936, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 64)
      - 1936-1937, Consumer newspaper (Box 64)
      - 1937, Consumer magazine (Box 64)
      - 1937-1950, Trade magazine (Box 64)
      - 1938, Consumer magazine (Box 64)
      - 1938-1940, Consumer newspaper (Box 64)
      - 1939, Consumer magazine (Box 64)
      - 1939-1940, Consumer magazine (Box 64)
      - 1940, Consumer magazine (Box 64)
      - 1940-1941, Consumer newspaper (Box 64)
      - 1941, Consumer magazine (Box 64)
      - 1942, Consumer magazine (Box 65)
      - 1942-1946, Consumer newspaper (Box 65)
      - 1943, Consumer magazine (Box 65)
      - 1944, Consumer magazine (Box 65)
      - 1945, Consumer magazine (Box 65)
      - 1946, Consumer magazine (Box 65)
      - 1947, Consumer magazine (Box 65)
      - 1947-1950, Consumer newspaper (Box 65)
      - 1948, Consumer magazine (Box 65)
      - 1949, Consumer magazine (Box 65)
      - 1950-1951, Consumer magazine (Box 65)
      - 1951, Consumer magazine (Box 65)
      - 1951-1952, Consumer newspaper (Box 65)
      - 1951-1952, Trade magazine (Box 65)
      - 1952, Consumer magazine (Box 65)
      - 1952-1953, Consumer magazine (Box 65)
      - 1953-1954, Consumer and trade magazine (Box 65)
      - 1954, Consumer magazine (Box 65)
    - Diamond Crystal salt
      - 1932-1933, Trade magazine (Box 66)
      - 1932-1939, Consumer newspaper (Box 66)
      - 1934, Trade magazine (Box 66)
      - 1935-1936, Trade magazine (Box 66)
      - 1937-1939, Trade magazine (Box 66)
      - 1938-1943, Trade newspaper (Box 66)
      - 1940-1941, Trade magazine (Box 66)
      - 1940-1944, Consumer newspaper (Box 66)
      - 1942-1943, Trade magazine (Box 66)
      - 1942-1945, Consumer magazine (Box 66)
      - 1943, Trade magazine (Box 66)
      - 1944-1945, Trade magazine (Box 66)
      - 1944-1946, Consumer newspaper (Box 66)
      - 1944-1955, Trade newspaper (Box 66)
      - 1945-1946, Trade magazine (Box 67)
      - 1946-1948, Consumer magazine (Box 67)
      - 1946-1948, Trade magazine (Box 67)
      - 1947-1950, Consumer newspaper (Box 67)
      - 1949-1951, Consumer magazine (Box 67)
      - 1949-1951, Trade magazine (Box 67)
      - 1951-1952, Consumer newspaper (Box 67)
      - 1952-1953, Consumer magazine (Box 67)
      - 1952-1953, Trade magazine (Box 67)
      - 1953-1955, Consumer newspaper (Box 67)
      - 1954-1955, Consumer magazine (Box 67)
      - 1954-1955, Trade magazine (Box 67)
    - Gaines dog food
      - 1944, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 67)
      - 1944-1946, Consumer and trade newspaper (Box 68)
      - 1944-1946, Trade magazine (Box 68)
      - 1945, Consumer magazine, 3 folders (Box 68)
      - 1948, Consumer magazine (Box 68)
      - 1948-1950, Consumer and trade newspaper (Box 68)
      - 1948-1949, Trade magazine (Box 68)
      - 1949, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 68)
      - 1950, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 68)
      - 1950, Trade magazine (Box 68)
      - 1951, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 68)
      - 1951-1953, Consumer newspaper (Box 69)
      - 1951, Trade magazine (Box 69)
      - 1952, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 69)
      - 1952-1953, Trade magazine (Box 69)
      - 1953, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 69)
      - 1954, Consumer magazine, 3 folders (Box 69)
      - 1954-1955, Consumer and trade newspaper (Box 69)
      - 1954-1957, Trade magazine (Box 69)
      - 1955, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 69)
      - 1956, Consumer magazine (Box 69)
      - 1956-1957, Consumer newspaper (Box 69)
      - 1957, Consumer magazine (Box 70)
      - 1958-1960, Consumer newspaper (Box 70)
      - 1959-1960, Consumer magazine (Box 70)
      - 1959-1961, Trade magazine (Box 70)
      - 1961-1964, Consumer magazine (Box 70)
      - 1961-1962, Consumer newspaper (Box 70)
      - 1962, Trade magazine (Box 70)
      - 1963-1965, Trade magazine (Box 70)
      - 1963-1977, Consumer newspaper (Box 70)
      - 1965-1971, Consumer magazine (Box 70)
      - 1966-1968, Trade magazine (Box 70)
      - 1969-1970, Trade magazine (Box 70)
      - 1972-1974, Consumer magazine (Box 70)
      - 1972-1977, Trade magazine (Box 70)
      - 1976-1980, Consumer magazine (Box 70)
      - 1978-1980, Trade magazine (Box 70)
    - Jell-O products
      - 1932-1941, Trade magazine (Box 71)
      - 1955-1963, Trade magazine (Box 71)
      - 1979-1982, Consumer magazine (Box 71)
      - 1981, Consumer newspaper (Box 71)
    - Log Cabin syrup
      - 1932-1939, Consumer magazine (Box 71)
      - 1932-1939, Consumer and trade newspaper (Box 71)
      - 1938-1949, Trade magazine (Box 71)
      - 1940-1941, Consumer magazine (Box 71)
      - 1947-1954, Consumer magazine (Box 71)
      - 1947-1953, Consumer and trade newspaper (Box 71)
      - 1950-1956, Trade magazine (Box 71)
    - Maxwell House coffee
      - 1932-1935, Consumer magazine (Box 71)
      - 1932-1935, Consumer newspaper (Box 71)
      - 1932-1935, Trade magazine (Box 71)
      - 1936-1939, Consumer magazine (Box 72)
      - 1936, Consumer newspaper (Box 72)
      - 1936-1939, Trade magazine (Box 72)
      - 1937-1939, Consumer newspaper (Box 72)
      - 1940-1943, Consumer newspaper (Box 72)
      - 1940-1942, Trade magazine (Box 72)
      - 1940-1942, Trade newspaper (Box 72)
      - 1940-1941, Trade magazine (Maxwell House tea) (Box 72)
      - 1941-1944, Consumer magazine (Box 72)
      - 1941, Consumer newspaper (Box 73)
      - 1943-1944, Consumer newspaper (Teem tea) (Box 73)
      - 1944, Consumer newspaper (Box 73)
      - 1945, Consumer magazine (Box 73)
      - 1945-1946, Consumer newspaper (Box 73)
      - 1945-1949, Consumer newspaper (instant coffee) (Box 73)
      - 1945-1959, Trade magazine (instant coffee) (Box 73)
      - 1945-1946, Trade newspaper (instant coffee) (Box 73)
      - 1946, Consumer magazine (Box 73)
      - 1946-1948, Consumer magazine (instant coffee) (Box 73)
      - 1947-1948, Consumer magazine (Box 73)
      - 1947-1948, Consumer newspaper (Box 74)
      - 1947-1948, Consumer magazine (Maxwell House tea) (Box 74)
      - 1947, Consumer newspaper (Maxwell House tea) (Box 74)
      - 1948, Trade: Salesperson newsletter (Box 74)
      - 1949, Consumer magazine (Box 74)
      - 1949-1950, Consumer newspaper (Box 74)
      - 1949-1950, Trade newspaper (Box 74)
      - 1950, Consumer magazine (Box 74)
      - 1950-1954, Consumer magazine (instant coffee) (Box 74)
      - 1950-1954, Consumer newspaper (instant coffee) (Box 74)
      - 1950-1953, Trade newspaper (instant coffee) (Box 74)
      - 1950-1952, Consumer newspaper (Maxwell House tea) (Box 74)
      - 1951, Consumer magazine (Box 74)
      - 1951, Consumer newspaper (Box 74)
      - 1952-1954, Consumer magazine (Box 74)
      - 1952-1954, Consumer newspaper (Box 75)
      - 1952-1954, Trade magazine (Box 75)
      - 1952, Consumer magazine (Maxwell House tea) (Box 75)
      - 1955-1958, Consumer magazine (Box 75)
      - 1955-1958, Consumer newspaper (Box 75)
      - 1955-1956, Trade magazine (Box 75)
      - 1957-1958, Trade magazine (Box 75)
      - 1957, Consumer magazine (instant coffee) (Box 75)
      - 1957-1958, Trade newspaper (instant coffee) (Box 75)
      - 1958, Consumer newspaper (instant coffee) (Box 75)
      - 1958, Trade: Collateral literature (Box 76)
      - 1959, Consumer magazine (instant coffee) (Box 76)
      - 1959, Consumer newspaper (instant coffee) (Box 76)
      - 1959, Trade magazine (instant coffee), 2 folders (Box 76)
      - 1959, Trade magazine (Box 76)
      - 1960-1964, Consumer magazine (instant coffee) (Box 76)
      - 1960-1961, Trade magazine (Box 76)
      - 1961-1962, Consumer newspaper (instant coffee) (Box 76)
      - 1963-1965, Trade magazine (Box 76)
      - 1965-1968, Consumer magazine (Box 76)
      - 1965-1968, Consumer newspaper (Box 76)
    - Post cereals
      - 1932-1933, Consumer (flattened cereal boxes) (Box 77)
      - 1932, Consumer magazine (Box 77)
      - 1932-1933, Consumer newspaper (Box 77)
      - 1934, Consumer magazine (Box 77)
      - 1934-1935, Consumer newspaper (Box 77)
      - 1934-1941, Trade newspaper (Box 77)
      - 1935, Consumer magazine (Box 77)
      - 1935-1939, Trade magazine (Box 77)
      - 1936, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 77)
      - 1936, Consumer newspaper, 3 folders (Box 77)
      - 1936-1937, Consumer newspaper (in Hebrew) (Box 77)
      - 1937, Consumer magazine (Box 78)
      - 1937, Consumer newspaper, 3 folders (Box 78)
      - 1938, Consumer magazine (Box 78)
      - 1938, Consumer newspaper (Box 78)
      - 1939, Consumer magazine (Box 78)
      - 1939, Consumer newspaper (Box 78)
      - 1940, Consumer magazine (Box 78)
      - 1940, Consumer newspaper (Box 78)
      - 1940-1941, Trade magazine (Box 78)
      - 1941, Consumer magazine (Box 78)